[
    {
        "question": "Which of these terms is associated with football?",
        "choices": [
            "Googly",
            "Scoop",
            "Free kick",
            "Birdie"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these terms is associated with cricket?",
        "choices": [
            "Googly",
            "Jab",
            "Scoop",
            "Free kick"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these terms is associated with hockey?",
        "choices": [
            "Googly",
            "Scoop",
            "Free kick",
            "Birdie"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these terms is associated with golf?",
        "choices": [
            "Googly",
            "Scoop",
            "Free kick",
            "Birdie"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these terms is associated with boxing?",
        "choices": [
            "Googly",
            "Jab",
            "Scoop",
            "Free kick"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens to a football player if they get a red card?",
        "choices": [
            "They get a warning.",
            "They get a yellow card.",
            "They have to leave the ground immediately.",
            "They get a penalty."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following terms is used in golf?",
        "choices": [
            "Scoop",
            "Penalty Corner",
            "Birdie",
            "Throw-in"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport uses the term 'Penalty Stroke'?",
        "choices": [
            "Cricket",
            "Football",
            "Hockey",
            "Boxing"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In which sport can a player get a 'Free kick'?",
        "choices": [
            "Golf",
            "Football",
            "Boxing",
            "Cricket"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport uses the term 'Jab'?",
        "choices": [
            "Football",
            "Hockey",
            "Boxing",
            "Cricket"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    }
]